{
    "id": "81c83e13256e472eb39a98a81a586ce5",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I shall ………………….. him if he …………………… .. to me for his misconduct.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pardon, commits",
                "forgive, apologizes",
                "reprimand, commands"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is natural …………………… a man to make mistakes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Lions roar, elephants …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bellow",
                "bleat",
                "grunt",
                "trumpet"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "If a candidate wants ………………….. as President, he / she must win the majority of votes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elected",
                "to be elected",
                "having elected"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words has the same meaning as the word ‘Conversant’?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "familiar",
                "pleasant",
                "ignorant"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The plane took ………………….. an hour …………………… its arrival.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "after, of",
                "off, after",
                "of, after",
                "off, on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was tired because I ………………… .. the whole day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was working",
                "had worked",
                "had been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Give the plural form of sheep",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Sheep",
                "Sheeps",
                "Sheepes"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Maiden speech means ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speech given by a maiden",
                "one’s first speech",
                "one’s last speech"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Though she refused first, she ………………….. in the end.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came about",
                "came off",
                "came out",
                "came around"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        }
    ]
}